[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "What does this mean for the peace process, for the Israelis, and the Palestinians?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "this", "mean", "for", "the", "peace", "process", ",", "for", "the", "Israelis", ",", "and", "the", "Palestinians", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "We want peace more than any other people.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "want", "peace", "more", "than", "any", "other", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "First I think it's a -- it's a terrible tragedy because everybody -- I look at the pictures in Japan and I think what every Israeli thinks and I think what every person in the world thinks, this could be us.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "--", "it", "'s", "a", "terrible", "tragedy", "because", "everybody", "--", "I", "look", "at", "the", "pictures", "in", "Japan", "and", "I", "think", "what", "every", "Israeli", "thinks", "and", "I", "think", "what", "every", "person", "in", "the", "world", "thinks", ",", "this", "could", "be", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Are you saying that you might actually stop any kind of nuclear energy program in Israel?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "saying", "that", "you", "might", "actually", "stop", "any", "kind", "of", "nuclear", "energy", "program", "in", "Israel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "We didn't have any civilian nuclear energy.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "did", "n't", "have", "any", "civilian", "nuclear", "energy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tunisia"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "And did you ever imagine that it would create the kind of domino effect we've been seeing?", "question_tokens": ["And", "did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "that", "it", "would", "create", "the", "kind", "of", "domino", "effect", "we", "'ve", "been", "seeing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "First, it didn't begin in Tunisia.", "answer_tokens": ["First", ",", "it", "did", "n't", "begin", "in", "Tunisia", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "What is -- what is the nightmare scenario for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "--", "what", "is", "the", "nightmare", "scenario", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "That you get another Iran.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "you", "get", "another", "Iran", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sadat"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "I mean to other people he may be a dictator, to Israel, he's been a pretty good friend, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "to", "other", "people", "he", "may", "be", "a", "dictator", ",", "to", "Israel", ",", "he", "'s", "been", "a", "pretty", "good", "friend", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Egypt under Sadat and then under Mubarak kept the peace and I think that's something extraordinarily valuable.", "answer_tokens": ["Egypt", "under", "Sadat", "and", "then", "under", "Mubarak", "kept", "the", "peace", "and", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "something", "extraordinarily", "valuable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Were you sad to see him go?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "sad", "to", "see", "him", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Well, I was -- I was concerned that we might have the opposite of what people want, and what we all want.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "--", "I", "was", "concerned", "that", "we", "might", "have", "the", "opposite", "of", "what", "people", "want", ",", "and", "what", "we", "all", "want", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"], "LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "What do you make of what's happening there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "'s", "happening", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Well, Gadhafi is no friend of Israel, no friend of the Jewish people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Gadhafi", "is", "no", "friend", "of", "Israel", ",", "no", "friend", "of", "the", "Jewish", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "What if he doesn't go?", "question_tokens": ["What", "if", "he", "does", "n't", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "ETANYAHU: I think -- I think the case of Libya is an interesting place where values and interests cohere.", "answer_tokens": ["ETANYAHU", ":", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "the", "case", "of", "Libya", "is", "an", "interesting", "place", "where", "values", "and", "interests", "cohere", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "DT", ":", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Is there not a moral compunction for America, for the West generally, to get in there and sort this out?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "not", "a", "moral", "compunction", "for", "America", ",", "for", "the", "West", "generally", ",", "to", "get", "in", "there", "and", "sort", "this", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "I think it's one of those cases where the moral compunction as you said and the -- and the interests cohere.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "one", "of", "those", "cases", "where", "the", "moral", "compunction", "as", "you", "said", "and", "the", "--", "and", "the", "interests", "cohere", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "If America decided to take military action, would you support that?", "question_tokens": ["If", "America", "decided", "to", "take", "military", "action", ",", "would", "you", "support", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Certainly wouldn't be against it.", "answer_tokens": ["Certainly", "would", "n't", "be", "against", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "I don't think it's surprising at all.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "surprising", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["U.S. Congress"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "I mean rather than wait for other countries to intervene on your behalf, what is Israel actually doing right now to combat this incredibly serious threat?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "rather", "than", "wait", "for", "other", "countries", "to", "intervene", "on", "your", "behalf", ",", "what", "is", "Israel", "actually", "doing", "right", "now", "to", "combat", "this", "incredibly", "serious", "threat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "Well, the first thing I've been trying to do for a long time, for -- you know, for about 15 years, I think, I was elected first time 15 years ago, and I went to speak at the -- before the joint session of the U.S. Congress.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "first", "thing", "I", "'ve", "been", "trying", "to", "do", "for", "a", "long", "time", ",", "for", "--", "you", "know", ",", "for", "about", "15", "years", ",", "I", "think", ",", "I", "was", "elected", "first", "time", "15", "years", "ago", ",", "and", "I", "went", "to", "speak", "at", "the", "--", "before", "the", "joint", "session", "of", "the", "U.S.", "Congress", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Do they have nuclear weapons, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "have", "nuclear", "weapons", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "It's working to get them.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "working", "to", "get", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "How close do you think they are?", "question_tokens": ["How", "close", "do", "you", "think", "they", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "I think they're getting a lot closer.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "'re", "getting", "a", "lot", "closer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Should they be transparent about their nuclear program?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "they", "be", "transparent", "about", "their", "nuclear", "program", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Even to the extent that they are transparent, it's very clear what they're doing.", "answer_tokens": ["Even", "to", "the", "extent", "that", "they", "are", "transparent", ",", "it", "'s", "very", "clear", "what", "they", "'re", "doing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "What are you doing about it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "doing", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Well, one of the things that we're telling people is that sanctions by themselves are not going to be enough.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "one", "of", "the", "things", "that", "we", "'re", "telling", "people", "is", "that", "sanctions", "by", "themselves", "are", "not", "going", "to", "be", "enough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Are you talking United Nations?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "talking", "United", "Nations", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "I'm talking about a credible military action that the --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "talking", "about", "a", "credible", "military", "action", "that", "the", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United Nations"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Led by who?", "question_tokens": ["Led", "by", "who", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Led preferably by the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["Led", "preferably", "by", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", ":", "CD", "NNP", "NNP"], "qSentId": 211, "question": "What does that constitute?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "constitute", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "It means action that will knock out their nuclear facilities and -- (CROSSTALK)", "answer_tokens": ["It", "means", "action", "that", "will", "knock", "out", "their", "nuclear", "facilities", "and", "--", "(", "CROSSTALK", ")"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Or could you contemplate some kind of land invasion?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "could", "you", "contemplate", "some", "kind", "of", "land", "invasion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Well, I think the United States has proven great effectiveness and I'm going to divulge a secret to you about their capabilities.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "United", "States", "has", "proven", "great", "effectiveness", "and", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "divulge", "a", "secret", "to", "you", "about", "their", "capabilities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "And you're still the number-one target, would you act unilaterally militarily?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "'re", "still", "the", "number-one", "target", ",", "would", "you", "act", "unilaterally", "militarily", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "No, we always reserve the right to defend ourselves.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "always", "reserve", "the", "right", "to", "defend", "ourselves", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Do you have nuclear weapons?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "nuclear", "weapons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Well, we have a longstanding policy that we won't be the first to introduce nuclear weapons into the Middle East, and that hasn't changed.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "have", "a", "longstanding", "policy", "that", "we", "wo", "n't", "be", "the", "first", "to", "introduce", "nuclear", "weapons", "into", "the", "Middle", "East", ",", "and", "that", "has", "n't", "changed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "So you don't have any?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "do", "n't", "have", "any", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "That's our policy.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "our", "policy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NPT"], "LOCATION": ["Iran"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "ORGAN: Is it right to expect countries like Iran to be transparent about their own nuclear programs if you're not transparent yourself?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Is", "it", "right", "to", "expect", "countries", "like", "Iran", "to", "be", "transparent", "about", "their", "own", "nuclear", "programs", "if", "you", "'re", "not", "transparent", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Well, Iran is a signatory to the NPT.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Iran", "is", "a", "signatory", "to", "the", "NPT", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "The nonproliferation treaty?", "question_tokens": ["The", "nonproliferation", "treaty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "I think it's ridiculous.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "ridiculous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "And where are you with the investigation into the perpetrators?", "question_tokens": ["And", "where", "are", "you", "with", "the", "investigation", "into", "the", "perpetrators", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "This was horrific.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "was", "horrific", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1993"], "LOCATION": ["Oslo"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Doesn't part of you, Benjamin Netanyahu, look at yourself and think, I want to be the guy that makes this happen, not the guy that didn't make it happen?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "part", "of", "you", ",", "Benjamin", "Netanyahu", ",", "look", "at", "yourself", "and", "think", ",", "I", "want", "to", "be", "the", "guy", "that", "makes", "this", "happen", ",", "not", "the", "guy", "that", "did", "n't", "make", "it", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Seven prime ministers have tried to get peace with the Palestinians since the peace process began in Oslo in 1993.", "answer_tokens": ["Seven", "prime", "ministers", "have", "tried", "to", "get", "peace", "with", "the", "Palestinians", "since", "the", "peace", "process", "began", "in", "Oslo", "in", "1993", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Benjamin Netanyahu"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "Honestly, what do I think?", "question_tokens": ["Honestly", ",", "what", "do", "I", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "And that could be you, couldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "could", "be", "you", ",", "could", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I'm pretty big.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "pretty", "big", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Doesn't history need people to be courageous?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "history", "need", "people", "to", "be", "courageous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "NN", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Yes, yes, it does.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", ",", "it", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"], "LOCATION": ["Israel", "Israel"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "CD", ":", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "WP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Why isn't it happening?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "n't", "it", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Because I think that Palestinian society is split into two; those who are openly calling for Israel's destruction, like Hamas, and those who not calling openly for Israel's destruction but refuse to confront those who do.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "think", "that", "Palestinian", "society", "is", "split", "into", "two", ";", "those", "who", "are", "openly", "calling", "for", "Israel", "'s", "destruction", ",", "like", "Hamas", ",", "and", "those", "who", "not", "calling", "openly", "for", "Israel", "'s", "destruction", "but", "refuse", "to", "confront", "those", "who", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 364, "question": "You were shot yourself?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "shot", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "I was shot rescuing --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "shot", "rescuing", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "Why would you want that legacy?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "want", "that", "legacy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "The legacy that I want is that I helped secure the life of the Jewish state and its future.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "legacy", "that", "I", "want", "is", "that", "I", "helped", "secure", "the", "life", "of", "the", "Jewish", "state", "and", "its", "future", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "The point I was making, though, is that it's no longer the only story in town, is it?", "question_tokens": ["The", "point", "I", "was", "making", ",", "though", ",", "is", "that", "it", "'s", "no", "longer", "the", "only", "story", "in", "town", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "No, it's not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Isn't that the perfect time to make this happen?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "the", "perfect", "time", "to", "make", "this", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "If you can be sure of who your partner will be tomorrow.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "you", "can", "be", "sure", "of", "who", "your", "partner", "will", "be", "tomorrow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["17 percent"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "There can't be, come on?", "question_tokens": ["There", "ca", "n't", "be", ",", "come", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Gaza's growing now at 17 percent because we lifted all the restrictions.", "answer_tokens": ["Gaza", "'s", "growing", "now", "at", "17", "percent", "because", "we", "lifted", "all", "the", "restrictions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "You wouldn't want your family living there, would you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "n't", "want", "your", "family", "living", "there", ",", "would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "EX", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "No, of course not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "of", "course", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Israel"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "NNPS", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "And if so, why?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "so", ",", "why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "First of all, there's a difference in the way that the Europeans view Israel and Americans view Israel.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "difference", "in", "the", "way", "that", "the", "Europeans", "view", "Israel", "and", "Americans", "view", "Israel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Where does that leave you?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "that", "leave", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "In fact, that's what they're doing.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "fact", ",", "that", "'s", "what", "they", "'re", "doing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "You can't bypass -- you can't bypass the parties to peace.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "ca", "n't", "bypass", "--", "you", "ca", "n't", "bypass", "the", "parties", "to", "peace", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "When is the last time you spoke to President Obama about this?", "question_tokens": ["When", "is", "the", "last", "time", "you", "spoke", "to", "President", "Obama", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "I speak to him regularly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "speak", "to", "him", "regularly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Israel"]}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Is he as supportive now as he's always been?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "as", "supportive", "now", "as", "he", "'s", "always", "been", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I think there's no question he's expressed his support for Israel, especially for Israel's security.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "'s", "no", "question", "he", "'s", "expressed", "his", "support", "for", "Israel", ",", "especially", "for", "Israel", "'s", "security", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "What can I do, President Obama, to help you, Prime Minister Netanyahu, make this deal happen?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "I", "do", ",", "President", "Obama", ",", "to", "help", "you", ",", "Prime", "Minister", "Netanyahu", ",", "make", "this", "deal", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "He's said that quite a few times.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "said", "that", "quite", "a", "few", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Netanyahu"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110317pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Well, if I end up meeting your expectations, you'll have to invite me back to another interview, won't you?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "I", "end", "up", "meeting", "your", "expectations", ",", "you", "'ll", "have", "to", "invite", "me", "back", "to", "another", "interview", ",", "wo", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "I will do that with great pleasure.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "will", "do", "that", "with", "great", "pleasure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]